# **Fadhil**

fadhilc97@gmail.com | LinkedIn | Website | Batam, Indonesia

## **Professional Summary**

The professional software developer with 4+ years experience to solve the business problem. Also have been as educator who like to share my knowledge and experiences about digital literacy, especially about programming fundamentals for 1.5 years experience. Now working as Front-end Developer in INCIT to develop assessment platform that help industrial transformation for their clients. As technology enthusiast, still passionate to keep up to date and utilize it to solve the real world problem, so it will increase the business productivity.

#### **Technical Skills**

Python, TypeScript, Node.is, PostgreSQL, Odoo (ERP), Express.is, React, Next.is, TailwindCSS

### **Work Experience**

## Front-end Developer (Full-time)

International Centre for Industrial Transformation (INCIT) - Hybrid

November 2022 - Present

Batam, Indonesia

- Implement the UI components and pages based on designed by UI/UX Designers
- Integrate REST API that already created with Backend Developer
- Collaborate with across functional teams: UI/UX Designers, Backend/Fullstack Developers, QAs, and Technical Writers

#### **Software Engineer (Full-time)**

PT. Tigernix Solutions Indonesia - Onsite

March 2020 - August 2022 (2 years 6 months)

Batam, Indonesia

- Develop and extend existing features in ERP application
- Provide data migration before live production
- Deployment setup using AWS EC2
- Create auto-backup database and attachment in server production with cron job and shell script

#### **Substitute Teacher (Part-time)**

SMK Multistudi High School - Onsite

August 2019 - December 2019 (5 months)

Batam, Indonesia

- Provide materials, examination questions and evaluation for Web and Mobile subject
- As a participant companion to participate the "LKS 2019" (student skill competition) Web and Technology competition Riau Island Province level for school representative.

#### IT Staff (Internship)

PT. Multi Kreasi Sinergia - Onsite

July 2018 - March 2019 (9 months)

Batam, Indonesia

- Handle the "Madebyme" makerspace
- Instructor of coding for kids
- Explore and prototyping related to robotic and IoT

#### **Education**

## **Batam State Polytechnic**

Diploma Degree in Informatics Engineering (GPA: 3.79)

Organization: Batam Linux User Group as Member of Programming Division